<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LKM Landing Page on LKM site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LKM Landing Page on LKM site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 13:36:26 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Collaboration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research/collaboration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 13:36:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research/collaboration/</guid>
      <description>Collaboration with academic institutions KU Leuven, Belgium University of Newcastle, Australia Technical University Graz, Austria South East European University, Macedonia TU Darmstadt, Germany University of Prizren, Kosovo University of Kragujevac, Serbia University of Hasselt, Belgium ASCR Institute of Computer Science, Czech Republic University of Malaga, Spain University of Porto, Portugal University of Ioannina, Greece Biotehnical Faculty, University of Ljubljana Faculty of Arts, University of Ljubljana FRI, Computer Vision Lab and Artificial Intelligence Lab University of Split, Croatia University of Novi sad, Serbia Collaboration with research institutions Jozef Stefan Institute; Department of knowledge technologies, Ljubljana The Laboratory of Neuroendocrinology - Molecular Cell Physiology; School of Medicine, Ljubljana Institute of Oncology, University Clinic Center, Ljubljana Clinic for Nuclear Medicine, University Clinic Center, Ljubljana Collaborators prof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guests</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research/guests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 13:36:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research/guests/</guid>
      <description>2022 Elyn Lemonnier (student) University of Polytech Clermont-Ferrand, France&#xA;8. 4. - 8. 8. 2022&#xA;2021 Prof. Mirjana Ivanović University of Novi Sad, Sebia&#xA;20. 6. – 25. 6. 2021&#xA;Tina Roland (student) University of Polytech Clermont-Ferrand, France&#xA;two months&#xA;Emile Poulain (student) University of Polytech Clermont-Ferrand, France&#xA;two months&#xA;2019 Prof. Mirjana Ivanović University of Novi Sad, Sebia&#xA;29. 9. – 5. 10. 2019&#xA;Kristian Miok Romania&#xA;3. 1. – 28.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 13:36:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research/projects/</guid>
      <description>Current and past projects Poročanje podatkov o kakovosti zraka in izdelava objektivnih ocen onesnaževal zraka 21. 01. 2021 - 28. 01. 2022&#xA;NexusLinguarum - European network for Web-centred linguistic data science Other international projects (NexusLinguarum) 28. 10. 2019 - 27. 10. 2023&#xA;RSDO - Razvoj slovenščine v digitalnem okolju Projects Structural Funds (RSDO) 01. 05. 2020 - 31. 08. 2022&#xA;Empirical foundations for digitally-supported development of writing skills Research projects ARRS 01.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selected References</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research/selected_references/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 13:36:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research/selected_references/</guid>
      <description>Journal Papers POLJAK, Mario, OŠTRBENK VALENČAK, Anja, ŠTRUMBELJ, Erik, MAVER VODIČAR, Polona, VEHOVAR, Vasja, RESMAN RUS, Katarina, KORVA, Miša, KNAP, Nataša, SEME, Katja, PETROVEC, Miroslav, ZUPAN, Blaž, DEMŠAR, Janez, KURDIJA, Slavko, AVŠIČ-ŽUPANC, Tatjana. Seroprevalence of severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 in Slovenia : results of two rounds of a nationwide population study on a probability-based sample, challenges and lessons learned. Clinical microbiology and infection : the official publication of the European society of clinical microbiology and infectious dieseases, ISSN 1198-743X, Jul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Location</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 12:06:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/location/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 12:06:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/presentations/</guid>
      <description>Presentation fliers LKM English flier (PDF, English) LKM Slovene flier (PDF, Slovene) PowerPoint Presentations LKM presentation (PPTX, English) Predstavitev LKM (PPTX, Slovene) Posters LKM Slovene poster (PDF, Slovene) Presentation of selected research topics (PPTX, Slovene) LKM intro Domen - Profiliranje spletnih uporabnikov Erik - Predstavitev Gregor - Predstavitev za LKM Haris - Predstavitev Igor - Določitev lokacije primarnega tumorja Igor - Modeliranje gibanja vodnih mas v Sredozemskem morju Igor - Povzemanje besedil Igor - Razlaga napovedi Jana - Prosojnice Kaja - Presentation AEE Marko - Projekt za informativni dan 2017 (1) Marko - Projekt za informativni dan 2017 (2) Martin - LKM presentation Matej - Učenje s kolonijo mravelj Matjaž - Proizvodnja elektrike in skoki Matjaž - Proizvodnja elektrike Miha - Analiza socialnih omrežij Petar - Modeliranje športa Zoran - Predstavitve projektov 2017 (ext) </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
